ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/081
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Dorothy Kaufman vs. Marilyn Eaves and Ottenheimer Brothers Manufacturing Company., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  1/66. Car accident between company employee and striker.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Cases related to picketing of Sears retail stores (carriers of Kellwood products). [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1969 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  11/66-12/69.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Cases related to picketing of Sears retail stores (carriers of Kellwood products). [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1969 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Cases related to picketing of Sears retail stores (carriers of Kellwood products). [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1969 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB case 26-CA-2560., 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  1/67-4/68. Alleged company wage increase to deter unionization at Alamo, Tennessee plant.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). U.S. Court of Appeals (6th Circuit) case No. 18,633., 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  6/68-3/69. Appeal of NLRB case 26- CA-2560 (Alamo, Tennessee).
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB case 26-CA-2681., 1967 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  2/67-3/67. Alleged company refusal to bargain.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Geraldine Booth, et al. vs. Frederick Siems, et al. Circuit Court, Sixth Judicial District, Pulaski County, Arkansas No. 68776., 1967- 1970 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  9/67-2/70. Car accident between plaintiffs and striker.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB case 26-CA-2967., 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  12/67-3/68. Alleged unfair appeal of striking employees' unemployment claims.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB case 26-CA-3072., 1968 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  5/68-6/68. Alleged unfair discharge of Robert Lee Thomasson.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Pearl Crook vs. George Lambert, et al. Circuit Court, Sixth Judicial District, Pulaski County, Arkansas No. 66579. [folder 1 of 3], 1968- 1969 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  5/68-3/69. Alleged injury caused by strikers against company supervisor.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Pearl Crook vs. George Lambert, et al. Circuit Court, Sixth Judicial District, Pulaski County, Arkansas No. 66579. [folder 2 of 3], 1968- 1969 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Pearl Crook vs. George Lambert, et al. Circuit Court, Sixth Judicial District, Pulaski County, Arkansas No. 66579. [folder 3 of 3], 1968- 1969 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB case 26-CA-3119., 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  7/68-4/71. Alleged refusal of company to reinstate strikers to the same or substantially similar jobs.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB cases 26-CA-3264, 26-CA-3284, 26-CA-3323., 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  8/68-2/69. Alleged company discriminatory discharges and refusal to rehire strikers.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB cases 26-CA-3264, 26-CA-3284, 26-CA-3323., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  2/69-4/69.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB cases 26-CA-3264, 26-CA-3284, 26-CA-3323., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  4/69-6/69.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB cases 26-CA-3264, 26-CA-3284, 26-CA-3323., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  6/69-10/69.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Leander Hayes vs. Sylvester Adams and Henderson Gaddy in the Circuit Court of Jefferson County, Arkansas., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  2/69. Car accident.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB case 26-CA-3397., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  6/69-9/69. Alleged company refusal to rehire strikers Bonnie Balding and Patsy Sue Williams.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). NLRB case 26-CA-3466., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  9/69. Alleged discriminatory discharge of Helen Crutcher.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Eva Chambers, et al. vs. Walter Tuck, et al. in the U.S. District Court for the Western District of Tennessee, Eastern Division, Civil Action No. 2121., 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  12/71-1/72. Union organizers' suit against city ordinance prohibiting distribution of literature in Dresden, Tennessee.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence before strike. [folder 1 of 4], 1966 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  3/66-10/66. Includes meeting notes and contract proposals.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence before strike. [folder 2 of 4], 1966 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence before strike. [folder 3 of 4], 1966 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence before strike. [folder 4 of 4], 1966 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence during strike., 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  11/66-8/67.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Union newsletters, leaflets, and propaganda before and during strike., 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  6/66-1/67.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence after U.S. Court of Appeals enforcement of NLRB's order to bargain., 1971 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  1/71-5/71.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence after U.S. Court of Appeals enforcement of NLRB's order to bargain., 1971 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  5/71-6/71.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence after U.S. Court of Appeals enforcement of NLRB's order to bargain., 1971 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  6/71-8/71.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence after U.S. Court of Appeals enforcement of NLRB's order to bargain. [folder 1 of 2], 1971 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  8/71.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence after U.S. Court of Appeals enforcement of NLRB's order to bargain. [folder 2 of 2], 1971 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Union newsletters, leaflets, and propaganda during negotiations., 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  12/70-8/71.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Contract administration correspondence., 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  11/71-12/73.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence (2nd round). [folder 1 of 4], 1974 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  4/74-9/74.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence (2nd round). [folder 2 of 4], 1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence (2nd round). [folder 3 of 4], 1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Negotiations correspondence (2nd round). [folder 4 of 4], 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Contract administration correspondence., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  2/79.
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Miscellaneous research. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Miscellaneous research. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Miscellaneous. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Kellwood (Little Rock). Miscellaneous. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  8/72-3/73. Includes Complaint and Notice of Hearing in Case Nos. 9- CB-2239, 9-CB-2276, and other early cases and orders.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  ?-7/76. Includes Amended Complaint in U.S. District Court, Western District of Kentucky at Bowling Green Civil Action No. 1638.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  7/76-8/76. Includes recommendation of John Doar.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1976 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  8/76-10/76. Includes chronology of events, Damage Interrogatories Propounded by Defendants to Plaintiff.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  10/76-1/77. Includes outlines of depositions of union witnesses.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  1/77. Includes Fourth Amended Counterclaim of Bobby Brooks, et al. Against the Plaintiff and the Rule 13 Defendants.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  1/77. Includes Rule 37 papers, Defendants' Memorandum in Support of Their Motion to Compel Discovery.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  1/77. Includes research on Kellwood, 2 copies of Kellwood's prospectus.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  1/77. Includes file of documents sent by Irwin H. Cutler.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  1/77-2/77. Includes chronology of events, Damage Interrogatories Propounded by Plaintiff to Defendants.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  2/77. Includes Plaintiff's Memorandum Brief in Opposition to Defendants' Motion to Compel Discovery Under Rule 37.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  2/77. Includes Answers and Objections to Damage Interrogatories Propounded by Plaintiff to Defendants and Attachments.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  2/77. Includes Transcript of the Deposition of Willa Dean Highbaugh.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  3/77. Includes affidavits of union witnesses.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  4/77-5/77. Includes first draft related to trial brief.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  6/77. Includes affidavits of union witnesses.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  7/77. Includes documents sent to U.S. District Judge Rhodes Bratcher.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files., 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  8/77-6/80. Includes various Kellwood financial statistics.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files. Statements for professional services., 1977-1981 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  2/77-1/81.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). John Doar's files. Information not supplied to company's counsel. (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). File of correspondence between Max Zimny and law firm of Segal, Isenberg, Sales and Stewart (primarily Irwin H. Cutler)., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  6/73-7/73. Includes company vs. ILGWU and officers.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Zimny and Cutler correspondence., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  8/73-12/73. Includes Order to Overrule Union's Motion to Quash and Dismiss Case.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Zimny and Cutler correspondence., 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  12/73-1/74. Includes interrogatories.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Zimny and Cutler correspondence., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  1/74-10/74. Includes Order for a Bifurcated Trial.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Zimny and Cutler correspondence., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  7/76-10/76. Includes affidavits of union witnesses.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Zimny and Cutler correspondence., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  10/76-11/76. Includes Lazare Teper's statistics on union's counterclaim, Final Pre-Trial Order.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Zimny and Cutler correspondence., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  12/76. Includes Response to Defendants' Request for Production of Documents, Plaintiff's Answers and Objections to Defendants' Damage Interrogatories.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Zimny and Cutler correspondence., 1976-1979 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  12/76-6/79. Includes affidavits of union witnesses.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Union's Motion for Summary Judgment file., 1976 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  4/76-8/76. Includes Motion for Summary Judgment, Affidavit of J. Craig Busey.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Union's Motion for Summary Judgment file., 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  9/76-1/77. Includes Memorandum Opinion and Order Denying Motion for Summary Judgment.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Union's Motion for Summary Judgment file., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  1/77-4/77. Includes Petition for Permission to Appeal.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Deposition of Neal E. Rakstang, division general manager. [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  10/74.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Deposition of Neal E. Rakstang, division general manager. [folder 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Deposition of Roy Lawrence Fruehauf, plant manager., 1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Deposition of Rick Jenkins, production supervisor., 1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Affidavit of Wilbur Daniels, Depositions of Sol C. Chaikin and Wilbur Daniels., 1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  3/76.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Deposition of Louis Stulberg and exhibits., 1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Legal fee statements, depositions., 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  8/72-4/76.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Continued Deposition of Wilbur Daniels., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  7/77.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Depositions of Harry Krugman and E. Howard Molisani., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Deposition of Milton Spitz and Continued Deposition of Sol Chaikin., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  10/77.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Deposition of Gus Tyler., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Deposition-related materials. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  Includes "A Guidebook for Union Organizers."
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Deposition-related materials., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  6/77-11/77. Includes copies of union LM-2 reports.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Exhibits accompanying deposition of Milton Spitz. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Exhibits accompanying deposition of Milton Spitz. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Miscellaneous deposition-related materials. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Miscellaneous deposition-related materials. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1974 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  3/74. Includes Plaintiff's Answers and Objections to Defendants' Interrogatories.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1974 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  3/74. Includes Exhibits of Plaintiff's Answers and Objections to Defendants' Interrogatories.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file. [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  7/74. Includes Answers and Objections to Plaintiff's First Interrogatories.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file. [folder 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  7/74. Includes Answers to First Interrogatories by Rule 13 Defendants to Counterclaimant International Ladies' Garment Workers Union.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  8/74-4/75. Includes Motion for Entry of Summary Judgment Dismissing Counterclaims.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file. [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  4/75. Includes Amended Answers to Plaintiff's First Interrogatories Nos. 17a, 20 and 28.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file. [folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  4/75-5/75. Includes Response to Plaintiff's First Request for Production of Documents.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1975 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  6/75-9/75. Includes Deposition of Willa Dean Highbaugh.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1975 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  9/75-12/75. Includes Motion for Entry of Order Approving Class Action [by company].
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  1/76-3/76. Includes company documents.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  3/76. Includes deposition of Frederick W. Wenzel.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  4/76-6/76. Includes Motion for Order Precluding Parties from Introducing Testimony of Defendant Highbaugh.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file. [folder 1 of 3], 1976 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  6/76. Includes affidavits of union witnesses.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file. [folder 2 of 3], 1976 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file. [folder 3 of 3], 1976 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  6/76. Includes Deposition of E.D. Johnson, Vice President in charge of the Calford Group.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  6/76. Includes Continued Deposition of E.D. Johnson.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  6/76-10/76. Includes Depositions of Ruby Geron and Robert Jenkins.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file. [folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  7/76. Includes Deposition of William S. Keeline.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file. [folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  10/76. Includes Damage Interrogatories Propounded by Defendants to Plaintiff.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file. [folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  10/76. Includes Deposition of Captain Ralph Cline.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file. [folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  10/76-1/77. Includes Deposition of Harold A. Franzman.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  1/77-3/77. Includes Damage Interrogatories Propounded by Plaintiff to Defendants.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1977 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1977 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  3/77-4/77. Includes Defendants' Answers and Objections to Plaintiff's Damage Interrogatories.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1977 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  5/77-6/77. Includes Defendants' Memorandum in Opposition to Plaintiff's Motion to Compel Discovery.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1977 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  7/77-11/77. Includes affidavits of union witnesses.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1977-1979 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  12/77-9/79. Includes chronology of strike activities.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1979 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  12/79. Includes Transcript of Hearing on Motions, Affidavit of John Doar.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  1/80-2/80. Includes Notice to Take Deposition of Willa Dean Highbaugh.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Damage Action Interrogatories file., 1980 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  2/80-3/80. Includes Affidavit of John Doar and Attachments.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Weekly reports of David Freeland, union organizer, during strike., 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  5/72-3/73.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Reports of Ruby Geron, union organizer, during strike., 1972 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  6/72-11/72.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Reports of Barbara Janis, union organizer, during strike., 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  5/72-2/73.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Strike disbursement receipts removed from damage action files., 1972-1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  9/72-3/76.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). List of Kellwood strikers and strike disbursements. (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Pre-trial conference file., 1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  3/78. Kellwood's Responsive Statements in Accordance with the Pre-Trial Conference Order of February 28, 1978.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Pre-trial conference file., 1978 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  3/78-4/78. Includes Defendants' Report to the Court.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Pre-trial conference file., 1978 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  4/78-5/78. Includes Transcript of Hearing at Pre-Trial Conference.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Pre-trial conference file., 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  6/78-8/79. Includes Defendants' Reply to Kellwood's Memoranda on Bifurcation and Defendants' Discovery.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Settlement papers file., 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  4/77-9/78. Includes preliminary analysis of plaintiff's summary of hard damages.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Settlement papers file., 1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  9/78-11/78. Includes agreement between Kellwood Company and Brownsville Manufacturing Company.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Settlement papers file., 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  7/79-3/80. Includes confidential resume of interview with David Freeland.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Settlement papers file. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  Includes settlement agreement.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Settlement papers file. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  Includes Ann Hoffman's notes.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Research on company. (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). National Credit Office reports on company., 1966-1973 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  12/66-7/73.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Daily schedule of Louis Stulberg. [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Daily schedule of Louis Stulberg. [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. General correspondence., 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  4/72- 1/73.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. NLRB cases 26-CA-3952 and 26-CA-4075., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  4/72-11/72. Alleged unfair labor practices by Kellwood at Greenfield and Dresden plants.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. Various handbills, court orders, and correspondence related to strike. [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  5/72-7/73.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. Various handbills, court orders, and correspondence related to strike. [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. NLRB case 9-CA-7115., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  6/72-8/72. Alleged illegal discharge of Ruth Hunt from Morgantown, Kentucky plant.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. NLRB case 9-CA-7171., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  7/72-9/72. Alleged harassment of strikers at Brownsville, Kentucky plant.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. NLRB case 9-RC-9653., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  7/72. Election case at Brownsville plant.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. NLRB cases 9-CB-2239 and 9-CB-2276., 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  7/72-8/73. Alleged union unfair labor practices at Brownsville plant.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. NLRB cases 9-CA-7087, 9-CA-7093-1-2-3-4, 9-CA-7234-1-2-3, 9-CA-7335. [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  7/72-5/74. Alleged company unfair labor practices at Brownsville plant.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. NLRB cases 9-CA-7087, 9-CA-7093-1-2-3-4, 9-CA-7234-1-2-3, 9-CA-7335. [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. NLRB case 9-CA-7311., 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  9/72-2/73. Alleged threats and offers of benefits by company at Brownsville plant.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. NLRB case 9-CA-7434-1-2., 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  11/72- 1/73. Alleged illegal discharges by company at Brownsville plant.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. Fairfield-Noble Corporation file., 1973 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  3/73.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Cases and correspondence related to damage action. Morgantown, Kentucky plant file., 1972-1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  7/72-9/76.